alrighty alrighty attention class  eyes up front please  as you might have heard the cultural  arts festival is coming up in just a few  days and the principal is expecting our  class to perform a play for the third  grade elementary school  because the drama club had to be close  to the recent coveted 19 outbreak  the teachers and i opted to use a raffle  to decide the cast this year  no way plays are for chicks  and not even the ones with big breasts  yes jared you teach can i draw one of  those raffle tickets  why certainly jared are you that  interested in joining the play yeah  something like that  [Music]  there you go parker take a big old whiff  of that big boy  [Applause]  now now kids i understand your sexual  frustrations but this is the only way to  do it since nobody in this class wants  to take the lead role i have no choice  but to do it like this  and everybody will have to participate  in some way if they don't want an f for  the semester  everyone reach intro the raffle and take  a slip of paper  and i don't want to hear any complaining  about what part you get  a cultural arts play huh  this is going to suck i wonder what kind  of play it's going to be but even though  it's just luck of the draw i guess we  would both like parts without too many  speaking lines huh  sonja take a ticket  knuckles you too  a bystander what intonation is that  supposed to be someone who works at a  cart and sells vegetables or something  it means you stand in the background and  do nothing  i don't want to [ __ ] do that i want a  cool part that will get [ __ ] on my  dick  well thank the harvest that's just what  i like to see everyone knows [ __ ]  love boys who can grow [ __ ] like corn  and carrots  hey max trade with me  what part did you get  a background extra  i'm in jared you're a lucky boy aren't  you  come on buddy do a bro solid here being  a farmer is my calling in life my  hillbilly dad will obviously come to  watch the play and i want to make him  proud mind making him watch me as i play  the fields with some dirty hoes  sorry jared  i would love to see you shirtless  and of course blow some hoss  but the teacher said we aren't allowed  to trade  i'm sorry  whatever max  yeah i'm sorry man like i said i would  tell you love to see you shirtless  give me that raffle ticket oh my god  teacher  your brother's cubby lasso to school  again  jared go put that lasso back in your  shoe cubby before i go over there and  take it away  dammit max you never miss a good chance  to shut up  you're lucky i ain't wearing my cowboy  boots with the spurs today  did everybody get their roles  when you get home remember to show your  parents  so they can help you with your costumes  here sonia i'm heading to the restroom  you wanna come with  sure let's go  me too i'll come with you girls  why do girls always go to the bathroom  together  i don't know probably a sex thing  i'm not saying this to embarrass you  but your hair makes your head look like  a hairy ball sack  hey fellas i'm going to drop some fat  poop in the outhouse do you wanna come  watch  not now jared maybe later  hey bro what part did you get  bro what's wrong  bro  what do those hedgehog eyes  [Music]  my bro is the lead are you kidding me  that role can he even do that he's a  [ __ ] dude  sonic do you want to decline  if you'd like you can trade with a girl  from the class  surely the crowd would rather watch a  princess with big tits  no i'll do it i'll play the role of the  princess i have to  i have to do it because  [Music]  up check it out there's a new sign on  the bathroom door what's it mean  i think it means it's for guys with big  fat butts  sweet looks like that's our call boys  big blue  are you sure about this  i mean i get that bartleby's the prince  but you shouldn't have to force yourself  to do it just because you're his  boyfriend  nobody ever said being gay was easy bro  i'll overcome this obstacle just like i  do any other you do realize you're gonna  have to wear a dress and everything the  whole school's gonna be there too you'll  be a laughingstock  don't listen to him sonic in fact i  think you will look pretty [ __ ] sexy  with the right dress and all that you're  so [ __ ] fat that you practically  already have boobies  damn it trevor i said stop hitting me  while i'm peeing in the urinal i pissed  all over my shoes again aside from that  why the hell are you three still here  you already peed shouldn't you be  getting back to class  don't even worry about that bro  sonia hold still i won't get the pin in  the right spot if you keep moving around  like a baby hedgehog that got into a bag  of sugar  i can't help it i'm just so excited  i wanna see haha well i guess it  wouldn't hurt for a quick preview go  ahead and take a look  is is this  me omg omg mom you're a miracle worker  i'm like so extremely totally gorgeous  but but i cannot help myself uncle  it's not fair that sonja's costume looks  so pretty despite only being a  background extra  why does mine look like a dirty stinky  potato sack i know i should have had mom  make it instead of your wrinkly ass you  won't fart yes yeah you did that i feel  sick  in the interview  well obviously your best isn't good  enough just get out of our house  do you know what i'll do it myself  no i'm saying i'll do it  don't pull away from me  [ __ ]  you can't believe you're well done it is  what does it matter it was going to look  like trash no matter what  mom should be making a dress for me not  that little pink [ __ ]  i'm the main character  yeah  would you monk let you  you know what  if you already was gonna yell  where are you going  you can't just leave me here with my  booty cheeks exposed for odyssey like  it's a juicy cheeseburger from burger  king  shut up  it's almost on september  [ __ ] you boomer yeah my brother doesn't  need your help [ __ ] bro help me down  from this box i gotta poop real bad oh  [ __ ] i'm not gonna make it bro get a  plastic sack  knuckles was right bro this was a stupid  idea  such a stupid stupid idea  i'm going to be a laughing stock in  front of everyone for wearing a dress  that looks like poop  there is no use crying over it now my  own bro  let us leave down for the night and get  some good sleep  perhaps if we are lucky uncle chuck  won't be so hungover tomorrow that he  can give it another shot  okay  if all else fails i would be honored to  let you wear my white beard and whitey  tighties instead  don't be afraid to ask  well it sounds like you kids got this  all figured out  now it's time for some shot i  oh i'm just so excited i know you're all  going to do just great tomorrow  night night mummy  night boys  night sonia  [Music]  [Music]  [Music]  wow knuckles you look great  how manly what a handsome soldier  don't go making this any more difficult  than it needs to be  that said this costume is really  realistic for some stupid play isn't it  of course it is did you really expect  anything less from the beauty club  i'm in the bakery club  nobody cares  i just thought they would like to know  well they don't  when mindy was making the costumes  she ran out of supplies and came by the  bakery club room i was making bread and  was like what do you need  you know like needing  [Music]  i was needing bread  flora just go before you embarrass  yourself more literally nobody finds you  funny  dear god sonic what the [ __ ] happened to  your costume you both look and smell  like crap  is it obvious  oh hell nah [ __ ] you [ __ ] stank  i'm so sorry everyone i know i let you  all down but i practiced all i could  and memorized all my lines i promise  i'll do whatever i can to make this show  a success  you can start by getting in a bathtub  and start cleaning that right trypass  no time for that everyone get in your  positions  the kids and parents are already  starting to lean up at the door  today's the day people  let's do our best and give it our all  today  [Applause]  thank you all for coming here tonight as  we dive into the story of love and  friendship  our wondrous tale begins in the  countryside just on the outskirts of the  sun kingdom  jared the farmer was hard at work  tending to his crops  oh man what chili wins today this season  has been tough for all of us so far but  at long last the seeds i have been  tending to all year round have begun to  sprout into plum beans  soon i will have enough beans to feed to  my family  that's my boy grow those beans you sexy  stuff of a man  but suddenly the farmer heard the  terrible sounds of marching coming from  the north  keep your dirty [ __ ] of my face farm  hand  i have never seen your faces in town  before  leave before i poop on your shoes  silence at once the prince bartleby has  decided to lay claim to your fields  the prince you save then why do i not  see a royal decree in our midst  the king's word is law surrender your  land  or pay dearly  nope  and with no more words to be spoken the  farmer was slain and but raped by the  prince's soldiers  wait what the hell  what incarnation yeah my boy you have to  be pooping in my cowboy hat you didn't  tell me you would die and get raped like  a [ __ ]  shut up dad i didn't know  i've always said this to you but for the  first time in my life i truly mean it  when i say you're a disappointment to me  boy  don't even bother coming home tonight  because you're sleeping in the barn with  the sheep  bring the script out here show me right  now where it says that the farmer is  [ __ ] or i'm not leaving  here on paper one that's fake you wrote  that yourself  you are raining the show climb off the  stage and don't let the door hit you on  the ass  what makes you think you have the right  to speak to me like that you're a nerd  this uniform says otherwise  someone get this country bumping off of  me  get that for australia get him stick  something up his ass or something  elena is this part of the play  well we are in a tamers one two three  four five video so it's certainly  possible  oh look there's sonja  okol and monica  i don't care much for that  please wait don't take our crops if you  do that we won't have anything to feed  the families of this poor town  oh yeah and how pray tell is that any of  the princes  please oh please good night  we have not gold nor silver to trade for  food is there anything else we might do  to change the prince's mind  ha how dare you stand in the princess  presents dressed in those filthy rags  i'll have you know disobedient sports  the prince is a crime punishable by that  but you won't hurt me  and what makes you so sure you peasant  do i have to spell it out it's cause  you're a knight and everyone knows  knights are meant to protect their  people and more importantly  [Music]  hmm  that handsome man over there the one  with the dress that shines like the  evening noon what is his name bring him  here i must learn his name at one  are you talking about the princess  princess nonsense i could see the  detailed outline of his ball sack  through the garment bring him before me  at once and be quick about it  watching him collect water into that  bucket like it is falling pee pee is  turning me on so [ __ ] much i demand  to pound his cheeks now  just roll with it bro  sir the prince requests an audience with  you get your butt here  an audience with little old me whatever  for  you called for me prince  my oh my you are even more dashing up  close and in person  i am having trouble right now just  keeping myself from raping you in this  very spot in fact i think i'm going to  take off your clothes and stick up your  ass  do you smell that  gross where is that smell coming from  i think it's that blue fat guy's dress  the one on stage  yuck it tricks like bear did someone  spill a can of bud light all over it  this is the worst play ever  i'm telling mommy and daddy to take me  home  [Music]  charles the show's not through yet where  are you going  the marketing's great  get out of this room old man  can't you see we're in the middle of  sewing club  yeah leave or else we are calling the  cops  oh  that's good you're going to need them  to survey you from me  [Music]  [Music]  and suck his wrinkly balls  i'm gonna rape him too  get your ass off my wife  [Applause]  [Music]  get out of here you're stinking up the  whole auditorium with those ranked  cheeks  [Applause]  stop  stop it  leave that man alone  quit throwing your trash my [ __ ] we did  what you wanted we put on this play for  you all are you not entertained is this  not why you are here  everyone throw your garbage at the sexy  man next  war bart levy is deflecting all of the  trash away with air pressure alone  by swinging his arms so fast  he's the fast switch your aim back to  sonic again  [Music]  [Music]  god  [Music]  dear boy if you wouldn't mind may i have  this done  [Music]  me  [Music]  you're the only thing i feel the only  thing i see  your lips like galaxy  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  i need  [Music]  do you remember  forever  [Music]  to save me  away  [Music]  is  [Music]  [Music]  you